<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>J Ford Tech &#8211; Smyrna, TN</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Computer Repair, Geek Services &#38; Handyman (&#38; Blog)</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 13:17:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/cropped-jIcon512-32x32.png</url>
	<title>J Ford Tech &#8211; Smyrna, TN</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Installing A Ring Doorbell In 10 Easy Steps</title>
		<link>/2023/04/06/installing-a-ring-doorbell-in-10-easy-steps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Justin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 13:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=59</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Installing a Ring doorbell camera is a straightforward process that can be completed in just a few simple steps. The following guide will provide an overview of how to install a Ring...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Installing a Ring doorbell camera is a straightforward process that can be completed in just a few simple steps. The following guide will provide an overview of how to install a Ring doorbell camera easily:<br></p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">1. Location</h2>



<p>Choose the right location for your Ring doorbell camera. Make sure it provides a clear view of the area you want to monitor and is easily accessible for installation and maintenance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">2. Charge</h2>



<p>Charge the battery. If your Ring doorbell camera has a rechargeable battery, charge it fully before starting the installation process.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">3. App</h2>



<p>Download the Ring app on your smartphone or tablet. The app is available for both Android and iOS devices and can be downloaded from the Google Play Store or Apple App Store.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">4. Account</h2>



<p>Create a Ring account or log in to your existing account using the Ring app.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">5. Instructions</h2>



<p>Follow the on-screen instructions in the app to set up your Ring doorbell camera. You&#8217;ll need to enter your Wi-Fi network name and password to connect your Ring device to your home network.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">6. Mount</h2>



<p>Install the mounting bracket provided with your Ring doorbell camera using the screws provided. Make sure it is securely attached to the wall or door frame.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">7. Attach</h2>



<p>Attach the Ring doorbell camera to the mounting bracket using the screws provided.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">8. Adjustment</h2>



<p>Adjust the camera angle as needed to ensure it is pointing in the right direction.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">9. Test</h2>



<p>Test your Ring doorbell camera by pressing the doorbell button or triggering the motion sensor. You should receive a notification on your smartphone or tablet and be able to see the live video feed from the camera.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">10. Tidy Up</h2>



<p>If everything is working correctly, finish the installation process by securing any loose wires or cables and adjusting the settings on the Ring app to customize your camera&#8217;s settings.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Congratulations!</h2>



<p>You have successfully installed your Ring doorbell camera and are ready to monitor your home from anywhere using your smartphone or tablet.</p>



<p>Alternatively, call me (Justin) today at <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="tel:239-391-4295" target="_blank">239-391-4295</a> and I will be happy to install your Doorbell Camera for you! Serving all Middle Tennessee.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Computer Tricks Everyone Should Know</title>
		<link>/2023/04/05/5-computer-tricks-everyone-should-know/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Justin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 16:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are so many tips, tricks and life-hacks when it comes to using your computer that it is impossible to memorize them all! Here are five that make my life easier on...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>There are so many tips, tricks and life-hacks when it comes to using your computer that it is impossible to memorize them all! Here are five that make my life easier on a daily basis and hopefully help you, too!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">1. Taking A Screenshot</h2>



<p>There are lots of programs out there that one can use to take a picture of the screen. This method involves opening a program, dragging an area to capture and choosing the location to save it to. Did you know there is a button right on you keyboard that does it in one click? The &#8220;Print Screen&#8221; key actually has a use! Just tap it!</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">2. Undo</h2>



<p>Almost every computer program, web browser and even OS (Windows, MAC and Linux) agree that ctrl + z is used to undo that last action. Sometimes will editing a photo, writing up a large document, etc. I will make a huge mistake like deleting an entire page in one click. Panic sets in, and then I remember holding down the ctrl key and pressing z will save the day. </p>


<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"><img decoding="async" width="420" height="294" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ctlrzLife.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-42" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ctlrzLife.jpg 420w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ctlrzLife-300x210.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 420px) 100vw, 420px" /></figure></div>


<h2 class="wp-block-heading">3. Window Snapping</h2>



<p>One of the features being introduced recently in Windows 11 is snapping windows to the top, bottom, left and right of the screen. This has been around for over a decade on Linux operating systems known as Tiling Windows. Just grab the tab or window and drag it where you want and it should snap automatically.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">4. Night Mode</h2>



<p>Staring at a screen on a dark room can cause serious eye strain and migraines. A feature that come out recently is Night Mode. Basically, it dims the blue light and reduces the discomfort.  Windows, MAC, Linux have this feature and even most phones. If your phone lacks this option, don&#8217;t worry, there are plenty of apps that will take care of it.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">5. Limiting Startup Programs</h2>



<p>Some computers seem to take forever to boot up after being turned on or after a restart! This is usually caused by many unnecessary programs starting when when the computer starts. Some good examples are Zoom, iTunes Helper, Adobe Reader and Microsoft Office. Most times we just want to open a browser to check the emails, watch some YouTube or check Facebook. We don&#8217;t need all these other apps slowing down the startup and slowing down the computer in general while they run in the background.</p>



<p>On Windows open the Task Manager, click the Startup tab and disable everything you don&#8217;t need.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="626" height="369" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/winStrtup.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-43" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/winStrtup.jpg 626w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/04/winStrtup-300x177.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 626px) 100vw, 626px" /></figure>



<p>On your Mac, choose Apple menu &gt; System Settings, click General in the sidebar, then click Login Items on the right. Remove what&#8217;s not needed.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img decoding="async" src="/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/macStrtup.png" alt="" class="wp-image-44" width="623" height="424" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/macStrtup.png 753w, /wp-content/uploads/2023/04/macStrtup-300x204.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 623px) 100vw, 623px" /></figure>



<p>Hopefully these tops save you some time and frustration. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>print (&#8220;Hello_World!&#8221;)</title>
		<link>/2023/04/05/hello-world/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Justin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Today is Launch Day for this new site, formerly TechUnlimitedUS.com. My name is Justin and I am a local Computer Repair, Tech Support Geek and Handyman based in Smyrna and serving all...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Today is Launch Day for this new site, formerly <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="http://techunlimitedus.com/" target="_blank">TechUnlimitedUS.com</a>. My name is Justin and I am a local Computer Repair, Tech Support Geek and Handyman based in <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.townofsmyrna.org/" target="_blank">Smyrna</a> and serving all of Middle Tennessee. I wanted more than just a static site listing my credentials and which services I offer, I wanted a place to share my experience and knowledge with anyone willing to listen, too. This site now serves both purposes! Feel free to drop me an email at <a href="mailto:TechUnlimited1337@gmail.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">TechUnlimited1337@gmail.com</a> if there is something you would like me to write about. Call me @ <a href="tel:239-391-4295">239-391-4295</a> for help with all your tech needs. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
